[
  {
    "question_no": 1,
    "question": "What is the name of this structure which is located in Piazza del Duomo, Italy?",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Colosseum",
      "option_2": "Leaning Tower of Pisa",
      "option_3": "Milan Cathedral",
      "option_4": "Ponte Vecchio"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_2"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 2,
    "question": "This famous statue located in New York City is referred to as?",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Spring Temple Buddha",
      "option_2": "Christ the Redeemer",
      "option_3": "Lion-man",
      "option_4": "Statue of Liberty"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_4"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 3,
    "question": "The structure below located in the Middle East was built thousands of years ago, and still stands today.",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Pharaoh’s Tomb",
      "option_2": "Joseph’s Tomb",
      "option_3": "Egyptian Pyramid",
      "option_4": "Mecca Temple"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_3"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 4,
    "question": "The highest mountain in the world, standing at 8,848 meters and 29,029 feet, with 145 attempts to climb it.",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Makalu",
      "option_2": "Nanga Parbat",
      "option_3": "Himalayan Mountains",
      "option_4": "Mount Everest"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_4"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 5,
    "question": "This is longest wall in the world.",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Kumbhalgarh Fort",
      "option_2": "Great Wall of China",
      "option_3": "Amer Fort Jaipur",
      "option_4": "Walls of Mesopotamia"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_2"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 6,
    "question": "This famed area is located in the mountains, at more than 2,400 metres/8,000 feet above sea level.",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Machu Picchu",
      "option_2": "Nazca Lines",
      "option_3": "Choquequirao",
      "option_4": "Chichen Itza"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_1"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 7,
    "question": "Shah Jahan instructed to build a tomb for his favorite wife, Mumtaz Mahal.",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "The Red Taj",
      "option_2": "Mizo Taj",
      "option_3": "Bibi Ka Maqbara",
      "option_4": "The Taj Mahal"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_4"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 8,
    "question": "The opera house was designed by Jørn Utzon from Denmark and it was built between 1959 and 1973.",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Teatro di San Carlo",
      "option_2": "Guangzhou Drama Center",
      "option_3": "Sydney Opera House",
      "option_4": "Bunkamura Orchard Hall"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_3"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 9,
    "question": " This famous American made car became the most popular car in the US in 1965",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Ford F-Series",
      "option_2": "Ford Mustang",
      "option_3": "Chevrolet Silverado",
      "option_4": "Chevrolet Tahoe"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_2"
  },
  {
    "question_no": 10,
    "question": "This specific breed of dog is often confused with a generic term for dogs, but is actually one specific breed.",
    "options": {
      "option_1": "Daschund",
      "option_2": "Pug",
      "option_3": "Beagle",
      "option_4": "Chihuahua"
    },
    "correct_option": "option_2"
  }
]
